Alexei Cocu

23.02.1986

I am an energetic, well-balanced and calm person with good communication skills and ability to cope with a dynamic working environment. A team player, people-oriented, loyal, organized and confident, always looking positively without going extreme or panic.

I discovered my passion for web development one year ago; It was then when it became clear what I wanted to do for a living. I pursued this path until I received enough confidence in HTML, CSS, JS. I took a beginner's online course, where I discovered the love for code. After that, I started the never-ending journey of becoming a frontend web developer along with sharpening my eye for backend.



+373 78 199 188

alexei.cocu@gmail.com

Married, 1 child

EXPERIENCE

Junior Web Developer Freelance
January 2020 – present

- Helping a team by working at different interesting small projects like web sites.
- Here I have learned the approximate workflow of creating a website from start till delivering to the client.
- Practiced GIT and started to learn Laravel.

Junior Web Developer Unemployed February 2019 – January 2020

- Strengthen the knowledge gained from theory through practice.
- Practicing "bootstrap", "node.js", "React", "Laravel" and "SQL".

IT PROFICIENCY

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript

SPOKEN LANGUAGES

- English
- Russian
- Romanian native

EDUCATION

Master degree

Business Administration 2008-2010

Bachelor degree

International Relations 2005 – 2008

COURSES

CodeCademy, Udemy, Interportal

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Laravel